plugco.in 2018-06-04

# The Plug

## Privacy Policy

### Last updated on March 7th, 2018

The Plug Privacy Policy explains how The Plug and parent company Real Labs Technology, Inc collects, uses, shares, and protects your information in relation to The Plug mobile and web services (“Service”). By using The Plug Service, you understand and agree to the terms and conditions of The Plug Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use (http://plugco.in/terms).

### Information Collection

We may collect and use the following types of information:

#### Account, Profile, and Contact information

When you create a The Plug account, we store the username, phone_number, password, and e-mail address you registered with the account. We also encourage our users to provide us with additional information such as a first and last name, a profile picture, a short description, a location. This optional information allows us to better respond to your requests, and makes it easier for other users of our Service to connect with you on The Plug. Any profile information that you provide us with may be updated or modified at any time.

If you choose to authenticate using a 3rd party supported service such as Facebook or Twitter, we will request access to public information from the connected account to help complete your The Plug profile.

We may use the contact information you provide us with to help connect you with other The Plug users.

#### Finding Friends feature

Mango includes functionality to locate other people you might already know in our network. You can decide to use this feature by providing us with information from your phone’s contact list, by searching for names or other keywords, or by connecting your The Plug account with other 3rd party services such as Facebook or Twitter. While connected to these services, you will be able to post your The Plug content to them as well. You may disconnect your The Plug account from the 3rd party services at any time.

### Location information

We recommend that users provide location information in their profiles, in order to better respond to their requests, and to allow other users of our Service to connect with them easier on The Plug. In addition, any of the content created in The Plug can be tagged with location information that is either obtained automatically (if user permitted) or set and/or modified manually by the user.

We may also use location information to display The Plug content that has been tagged near your location.

### Device information

We may access, collect, and/or remotely store miscellaneous device information, such as your device’s unique identifier, operating system, and mobile network information, in order to help us to provide better support for you.

### Log data

When you use our Services, we automatically record log data created by your use of the Services. This data may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser type, your web request, number of clicks, pages and links visited, search terms, cookie information, and other such information regarding how you interact with our Services.

The Plug uses log data in order to measure and improve its Services.

### Information Usage and Sharing

We use information that you provide us with to:

\- make sure that our Services are working in the most effective manner for you

\- remember information so that you won’t have to re-enter it the next time you use our Services

\- provide you with information, products, or services that you either requested from us or have consented to be contacted for

\- identify, diagnose, and fix problems related to the effectiveness of our Services

\- notify you about any updates or changes to our Services

\- We will not sell or rent your information to any third parties outside The Plug and its parent company, Mango Labs, LLC, without your consent, except as noted in this Policy.

We may disclose your information to such third parties if we are under a duty to do so in order to comply with any legal obligation (such as a search warrant, court order, or a subpoena). In case a part of or the whole set of The Plug assets is sold or transferred to another organization, your information may be among the items sold or transferred. In addition, we may engage third party service providers to facilitate normal operation of our Services, and we may share some of your information with them, subject to the confidentiality obligations consistent in this Policy.

The information provided to us can be modified by you through tools and settings available as part of our Services. You can also permanently delete your The Plug account by contacting us.

### Data Retention

If you'd like us to delete Content that you have provided via Services, please contact us and we will respond in a reasonable time and process the request in accordance with our Terms of Use.

Certain information pertaining to your use of our Services may be used and disclosed, during and after the term of the Services, in aggregate. We also may use this information internally to conduct benchmark analysis or industry-based results pertaining to our Services. This aggregate information cannot be used to personally identify you, your business, or your computer.

### Children’s Privacy

The Plug Services and content are not directed at persons under the age of 13, and we knowingly do not allow such persons to register for the Service. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us, and we will take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.

### Changes to our Policy

We may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Even though we will provide forms of notice as appropriate under the circumstances, please review the Policy directly periodically.

Your continued use of The Plug or the Service after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification. The most current version of the policy will always be available at http://plugco.in/privacy.
